A Guide to the John M. Sherwood Collection, circa 1860-2011
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The John M. Sherwood Collection, circa 1860-2011
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 07-15
Approx. 14 linear ft.; 22 boxes, 5 map drawers
This collection contains correspondence, legal documents, blueprints, plats photographs and artifacts from the personal and professional lives of the Sherwood and Myers families in Fairfax County, Virginia. The materials date from circa 1860 to 2011.
John M. Sherwood
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Gift of John M. Sherwood in 2008 and 2009.
Historical and Biographical Information
Albert Reuben Sherwood was born on January 8, 1879 near Hope Park in Fairfax County. With no formal schooling, he taught himself reading, penmanship, and architectural drawing. Sherwood initially made his living purchasing property, removing timber for sale, and re-selling the property for a profit. While operating a sawmill at Tyson's Crossroads, he met his wife, Annie Belle Myers. The couple moved to the Town of Fairfax, where Mrs. Sherwood ran Sherwood's Tourist Home and Kamp Washington tourist court. Albert Sherwood went on to found a successful construction company, taking commercial and private contracts throughout northern Virginia. Albert served for forty years on the Fairfax Town Council, just before its transition from a town to a city. He sat on the board of directors of The National Bank of Fairfax until his death in 1963. Albert and Annie had four children: Ruth Janet (1914-2000), Albert Maurice (1916-1943), John Myers (1919-2010) and Stacy Charles (1922-2002).
John Myers Sherwood was born in the Town of Fairfax, on August 21, 1919. He attended Fairfax High School, where he was a member of the first graduating class in 1936. He went on to study at The University of Virginia and graduated from the McIntire School of Commerce in 1940. After college, Sherwood was drafted into military service. He spent the duration of World War II in England as an ordnance officer with the 8th Air Force. Upon returning home, he began his professional career in the office of the Fairfax County Commissioner of the Revenue. His public service continued for fifteen years on the Fairfax Board of Zoning Appeals. He vacated his seat in 1967, upon moving from Fairfax City to Fairfax County. Sherwood's banking career began at The Vienna Trust Company in 1949. He became president of The First National Bank of Quantico in 1968 and went on to The Citizens National Bank of Herndon, where he remained until 1977. He founded The George Mason Bank in 1978 and served as the President and CEO until his retirement in 1991. John was also instrumental in the formation of EZ Communications, the ultimate development of Fairfax's original WEEL radio. He served on the board at EZ until the company was sold in 1996. Sherwood was a founding member of the The Country Club of Fairfax, and served on their board for many years. He remained a member until his death in 2010. He married Nan Edna Wolfe in 1949 and their union lasted until her death in 1998. The couple had two daughters, Valerie Sherwood Ford and Nadine Sherwood Stow.
Scope and Content
Series 1: Papers, 1861-2011
Subseries 1-1: Albert Reuben Sherwood, 1911-1968
This subseries includes documents from Albert Sherwood's time on the Fairfax Town Council, real estate loan and sales documents, ephemera and related items from the National Bank of Fairfax, along with numerous invoices, receipts and miscellaneous papers from the early to mid 1900s.
Subseries 1-2: John Myers Sherwood, 1928-1999
This subseries is highlighted by correspondence from his years at The University of Virginia and during his service in Europe during World War II.
Subseries 1-3: Ruth Janet Sherwood, 1921-1945
This subseries contains personal papers from Albert and Annie Sherwood's daughter, Ruth.
Subseries 1-4: Stacy Charles Sherwood, 1930-2011
This subseries contains personal papers from Albert and Annie Sherwood's son, Stacy.
Subseries 1-5: Albert Maurice Sherwood, 1923-1943
This subseries contains personal papers from Albert and Annie Sherwood's son, Maurice.
Subseries 1-6: Sherwood Family, 1910-1998
This subseries features general miscellaneous items from the Sherwood family, including social invitations and correspondence.
Subseries 1-7: Myers Family, 1861-1972
This subseries contains items from the Myers family of Maryland and later Tyson's Corner, Virginia. The series is contained in ten boxes.
Series 2: Photographs, 1860-1989
Subseries 2-1: Sherwood, 1910-1989
This subseries contains numerous snapshots of daily life around the Sherwood home on Main Street in Fairfax during the early 1900s. Also included are photographs of properties owned by Albert and John Sherwood, along with personal photographs.
Subseries 2-2: Myers, 1860-1969
This subseries is comprised personal photographs and portraits of the Myers family, along with images of their property in Tyson's Corner, Virginia from the beginning to the middle of the twentieth century. The series is contained in four boxes.
Series 3: Oversize, 1920-1983
This series features plats and architectural drawings related to projects executed by Albert Sherwood's construction company, along with plans for The George Mason Bank and other projects that John Sherwood was involved in. The items are contained in four map case drawers, with a few very large items stored under the table in the rare book room's processing area. Five framed items sit on the rear shelves in the manuscript storage area of the rare book room.
Series 4: Realia, 1868-1980
This series includes ephemeral advertising items from locally owned Fairfax businesses, items from the Myers store in Tyson's corner and a metal road sign from the Kamp Washington tourist court in Fairfax. It is contained in nine boxes and one map drawer.
Arrangement
Papers are arranged by person and chronologically. Photographs are arranged by family and chronologically. Oversize items and realia are organized chronologically.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Sherwood, Albert Reuben; Sherwood, Annie Myers; Sherwood, John Myers; Sherwood, Ruth Janet; Sherwood, Stacy Charles; Sherwood, Albert Maurice; Farr, Wilson Mahone; Patram, William "Wild Bill"; Wood, John Clinton; City of Fairfax, Virginia; Town of Fairfax, Virginia; Fairfax County, Virginia; Kamp Washington; Tyson's Corner
Container List
- Series 1: Papers, 1861-2011
  - Subseries 1.1: Albert Reuben Sherwood, 1911-1968
    - Construction log book, 1911-1914 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous deeds, 1913-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Construction log book, 1914-1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Town of Fairfax and Fairfax County tax bills, 1917-1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Promissory notes and loan documents, 1918-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - National Bank of Fairfax, miscellaneous items, ephemera (1 of 2), 1918-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - National Bank of Fairfax, annual reports, statements of condition (2 of 2), 1919-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Log book, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Unused stationery and forms, circa 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Insurance policy on residence, 1923-1928 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Receipts and invoices, 1926-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Articles of incorporation, Sherwood Construction Corp., 1926 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - State license applications for lodging house, 1928-1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Log book for Clarenford construction job, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Guest register, Sherwood's Tourist Home, 1931-1951 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policy on grocery store, Fairfax, 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sherwood's Tourist Home, miscellaneous, 1932-1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Financial statements, 1932-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Lease agreement, blotter, sales agreement, Dewey Thomas, Fairfax Motors, 1933-1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Construction log book with entries for "School at Fairfax" and "School Centreville job", circa 1934 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Specifications for house for Mrs. Sue Thompson, Highland Park, Arlington, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Plats, copies of house plans from plan books, 1936-1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ledger of business accounts, 1937-1954 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Harold and Carmen Weiler, 1937-1959 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Lease to Malcolm Proudfoot for house in Moore and Oliver subdivision, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and sales agreements with W.S. Hoge Jr. and W.S. Hoge III, 1938-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Deed of trust, property in Fairfax, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Building permits, construction documents, Westmore and Fairfax Heights subdivisions, 1940-1953 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Letter from W.T. Woodson regarding heaters Fairfax High School auditorium, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Letter and deed from Mavis C. Cobb regarding property sale for state highway, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - World War II ration books for Sherwood tenants, 1941-1945 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence with Wilson M. Farr regarding loans, 1941-1956 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Federal income tax returns, Sherwood Construction Corp., 1941-1957 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with Viola Farr Orr regarding insurance on lots in Fairfax Heights subdivision, 1942-1947 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - John J. DePorry, sale of property in Westmore subdivision, 1944-1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Sales flyer for Cobbdale subdivision, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Purchase farm, Loudoun County, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Sale of lots in Fairfax Heights subdivision to Fairfax Baptist Church, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Certificate of title, Kamp Washington property, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Garage rental to C&P Telephone, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Loan to Richard W. Huntt, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Capon Bridge Farm, West Virginia, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with tenants, 1950-1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Sale of Burke tract to Wood, Bauknight, et al., 1950-1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Loan statements from Wilson M. Farr and John Rothrock, 1950-1958 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Receipts for property appraisals by Albert R. Sherwood on behalf of The National Bank of Fairfax, 1951-1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Insurance survey of Kamp Washington with pasted in photographs, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence regarding inspections of addition to Fairfax County Courthouse, 1952-1952 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Litigation with the Texas Company (Texaco), 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Receipts for construction materials, duplexes on Park Road, Westmore subdivision, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Invoices for construction materials, homes in Westmore subdivision, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Sale of Magner Farm tract to Braddock Land Company, 1953-1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Sale of parcels in Fairfax to Miller and Rubin, 1955-1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Purchase, sale, repurchase and resale of lots 7 and 8, Westmore section 4, 1955-1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Tax bill for farm, Harper's Ferry, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Injury of Eddie Fagan, Sherwood employee, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Letter with plat from John Rothrock regarding loan for proposed Fairview Shopping Center, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Ledger of household accounts, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sale of Westmore duplexes to Iliff, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous documents, Sherwood and Farr heirs Kamp Washington property, 1961-1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous documents, Smith's Frozen Custard, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Specifications for renovation of home in Warrenton, Virginia, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Fairfax Town Council (1 of 2), 1948-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax Town Council (2 of 2), 1950-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Q&A from John C. Wood regarding proposed expansion of water system, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Membership cards, ephemera, 1918-1939 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Motor vehicle related documents, 1920-1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Petition to Fairfax town council for widening of Keith Avenue, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Depression era poem, "Hoover is now my Shepherd", circa 1930-1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - World War II ration items, circa 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous documents, Roberta Jones, housekeeper, 1950-1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Dr. Elmar Stebbins Waring, checks, bill, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Checks to neighbor Henry "Chip" Dewey, for lawnmowing, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Albert and Annie Sherwood, deaths, funerals, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Albert Sherwood, miscellaneous handwritten notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Federal and state income tax returns, 1940-1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Federal and state income tax returns, 1948-1955 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Federal and state income tax returns, 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Federal and state income tax returns, 1959-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.2: John Myers Sherwood, 1928-1999
    - Purchase and sale of home on Chestnut Street, Westmore subdivision, 1949-1955 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lots in Fairfax Heights subdivision, 1951-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Other properties, 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Vienna Trust Company, 1952-1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Estate of Hugh "Ike" Jordan (1 of 2), 1955-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Estate of Hugh "Ike" Jordan (2 of 2), 1955-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Shirley Gate properties, 1955-1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Relocation of John Sherwood home, Albert R. Sherwood residence by William B. Patram, 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Service on Fairfax Town and City Board of Zoning Appeals, 1960-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Sales brochure, Fairfax Villa subdivision, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Potomac Bank and Trust, annual reports and related documents, 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous documents related to banking career, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Kamp Washington property, potential purchase contracts and related documents, 1966-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Financial reports and income tax returns, MainOak Enterprises (1 of 2), 1973-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Financial reports and income tax returns, MainOak Enterprises (2 of 2), 1975-1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Annual reports, EZ Communications (1 of 2), 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Annual reports, EZ Communications (2 of 2), 1982-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - MainOak Enterprises, correspondence regarding proposed office complex, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Startup documents, clippings, George Mason Bank, 1977-1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence regarding proposed building renovation, EZ Communications, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Annual reports, George Mason Bank (1 of 2), 1979-1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Annual reports, George Mason Bank (2 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Consolidated financial reports, George Mason Bank, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous ephemera, George Mason Bank, 1981-1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - George Mason Bank, possible lease of McCandlish property, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - City of Fairfax Economic Development Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Article published in Virginia Accountant Quarterly, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Booklet entitled "Capsized" by John D. Ringle, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - WEZR ephemera, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Dr. E.S. Waring instructions for John Sherwood, rheumatic fever, circa 1920 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Report cards, 4th and 5th grade, 1928-1930 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Certificates and diplomas, 1932-1936 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax High School class of 1936, calling cards, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Letters home from The University of Virginia (1 of 2), 1936 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Letters home from The University of Virginia (2 of 2), 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - University of Virginia, report cards, transcripts and documents, 1936-1943 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - John Sherwood, Stacy Sherwood World War II sugar ration coupons, circa 1941-1945 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Fairfax High School Alumni Association meeting minutes, membership lists, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (from John Sherwood), 1941-1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Virginia state teachers certificates, Nan Edna Wolfe, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (to John Sherwood), 1943-1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Christmas Greeting, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous personal, 1946-2010 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Original poem, "Just Thinking", 1948 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Court House Country Club membership directories, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Financial statements, 1954-1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Nadine and Valerie Sherwood, grade school materials, 1959-1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Oakton, Fairfax High School reunions, 1985-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax High School class of 1936, 50th reunion booklet, clipping, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Historic Fairfax City Inc., newsletter, Christmas ornament, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.3: Ruth Janet Sherwood, 1921-1945
    - Report cards, 1921-1929 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1963 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Report cards, University of Richmond, Westhampton College, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Ruth Sherwood, World War II ration books, circa 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - James J. Corbalis, World War II ration books, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax Cemetery, receipts and disbursements, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 1.4: Stacy Charles Sherwood, 1930-2011
    - National Bank of Fairfax savings account passbook, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Applications for dog licenses, 1932-1937 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1943 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Grand opening invitation and program, Stacy C. Sherwood Community Center, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 1.5: Albert Maurice Sherwood, 1923-1943
    - Report cards, 1923-1940 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Postcards, misc., 1930-1940 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Oakton High School diploma, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Handwritten graduation speech, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Letter from Wilson M. Farr regarding Farr Building, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Letters home from The University of Virginia, 1937-1940 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1943 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 1.6: Sherwood Family, 1910-1998
    - Social invitations, 1910-1978 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1913-1943 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Fairfax Cemetery receipts, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Fairfax Methodist Church, 1919-1961 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Clippings, 1930-1998 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Local ephemera, 1936-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Building supply catalogs from local stores, 1952-1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.7: Myers Family, 1861-1972
    - Civil War song, circa 1861-1865 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Letter from James Myers, 1863 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Family letter, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Letter from Susan Shaw, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Business correspondence, 1874-1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Savilla C. Myers, dog license, calling cards, contract for purchase of automobile, 1894-1931 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1902-1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Tyson's Corner Garage, advertising calendar notebooks, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Birth, death and marriage records, 1923-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Charles K. Myers, judgement against, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Leases, 1937-1957 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with Wilson M. Farr, 1940-1944 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Ration books, circa 1941-1945 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Deeds of trust, survey documents, 1942-1956 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Insurance documents, county tax bills, 1945-1957 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Myers trust, federal and state income tax returns, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Estates of Savilla Myers and Charles Myers, 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Sale of right of way to United States government, 1951-1958 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Condemnation of property at Tyson's Corner, 1962-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Series 2: Photographs, 1860-1989
  - Subseries 2.1: Sherwood, 1910-1989
    - Albert and Annie Sherwood, circa 1920-1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - National Bank of Fairfax, 1931-1953 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Ruth Sherwood, circa 1929-1949 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Maurice and Victory Sherwood, circa 1910-1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - John Sherwood, circa 1920-1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Board of Zoning Appeals, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Vienna Trust Company, circa 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - John M. Sherwood Birthplace, Main Street, Fairfax, circa 1920-1929 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - John M. Sherwood, banking functions, bankers' associations, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - George Mason Bank (1 of 2), circa 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - George Mason Bank (2 of 2), circa 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Stacy Sherwood, circa 1920-1989 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Ten cent car, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous groups, circa 1910-1949 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Friends and other family, circa 1910-1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Two different postcards, Fairfax Courthouse, circa 1900-1909 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Dandridge house, circa 1920-1939 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Birkett House, circa 1930-1939 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Tavern, circa 1930-1939 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Houses built by Sherwood Construction Corp. at Moore and Oliver Streets, Fairfax, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - House built by Luther R. Sherwood Construction, unknown location, circa 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Hope Park, circa 1950-1969 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Westmore subdivision, Fairfax, circa 1940-1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Albert R. Sherwood residence at Kamp Washington, circa 1930-1969 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Sherwood houses at Kamp Washington being moved by William B. Patram, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sherwood property at Kamp Washington, circa 1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Flint Hill School building being moved by William B. Patram, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Sherwood and Myers unknown, circa 1880-1920 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sherwood and Myers unknown, circa 1900-1939 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Sherwood negatives, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2.2: Myers, 1860-1969
    - Savilla Myers, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Mack and Gladys Myers, circa 1900-1905 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Stacy Myers, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Myers family and friends, circa 1900-1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Myers unknown (1 of 2), circa 1860-1929 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Myers unknown (2 of 2), circa 1860-1929 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - George Washington Monument, Boonsboro, Maryland, circa 1930-1939 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Myers property at Tyson's Corner, circa 1905-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Interior of Myers store at Tyson's Corner (4 copies, mounted on boards and curled), circa 1920-1939 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Oversize, 1920-1983
  - Brochures, circa 1920-circa 1969 (Drawer 1, Folder 1)
  - Westmore subdivision, 1927-1953 (Drawer 1, Folder 2)
  - Westmore subdivision, 1947-1951 (Drawer 1, Folder 3)
  - Kamp Washington, 1950-1972 (Drawer 1, Folder 4)
  - Kamp Washington and unknown, circa 1936 (Drawer 1, Folder 5)
  - Kamp Washington, 1970 (Drawer 1, Folder 6)
  - Six room house for Mrs. Sue Thompson, 1931 (Drawer 2, Folder 1)
  - Floorplans, 1929 (Drawer 2, Folder 2)
  - Floorplans, 1930 (Drawer 2, Folder 3)
  - Plats, 1927-1978 (Drawer 3, Folder 1)
  - Plats, 1923-1983 (Drawer 3, Folder 2)
  - Mail order house plans, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 3)